{
	"deck": [
		{
			"prompt": "pwd",
			"answer": "print working directory"
		},
		{
			"prompt": "hostname",
			"answer": "my computer's network name"
		},
		{
			"prompt": "mkdir",
			"answer": "make directory"
		},
		{
			"prompt": "cd",
			"answer": "change directory"
		},
		{
			"prompt": "ls",
			"answer": "list directory"
		},
		{
			"prompt": "rmdir",
			"answer": "remove directory"
		},
		{
			"prompt": "pushd",
			"answer": "push directory"
		},
		{
			"prompt": "popd",
			"answer": "pop directory"
		},
		{
			"prompt": "cp",
			"answer": "copy a file or directory"
		},
		{
			"prompt": "mv",
			"answer": "move a file or directory"
		},
		{
			"prompt": "less",
			"answer": "page through a file"
		},
		{
			"prompt": "cat",
			"answer": "print the whole file"
		},
		{
			"prompt": "xargs",
			"answer": "execute arguments"
		},
		{
			"prompt": "find",
			"answer": "find files"
		},
		{
			"prompt": "grep",
			"answer": "find things inside files"
		},
		{
			"prompt": "man",
			"answer": "read a manual page"
		},
		{
			"prompt": "apropos",
			"answer": "find what man page is appropriate"
		},
		{
			"prompt": "env",
			"answer": "look at your environment"
		},
		{
			"prompt": "echo",
			"answer": "print some arguments"
		},
		{
			"prompt": "export",
			"answer": "export/set a new environment variable"
		},
		{
			"prompt": "exit",
			"answer": "exit the shell"
		},
		{
			"prompt": "sudo",
			"answer": "DANGER! become super user root DANGER!"
		},
		{
			"prompt": "chmod",
			"answer": "change permission modifiers"
		},
		{
			"prompt": "chown",
			"answer": "change ownership"
		}
	]
}